import { QuestionType } from "../../components/question/multipleChoice";

export const multiplyDivideQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 75 x 10?",
  options: ["750", "7.5", "7500", "75"],
  answer: "750",
};
export const multiplyDivideQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 123 × 100?",
  options: ["1230", "12300", "123000", "123"],
  answer: "12300",
};

export const multiplyDivideQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 8.5 × 1000?",
  options: ["85", "850", "8500", "85000"],
  answer: "8500",
};

export const multiplyDivideQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 0.47 × 100?",
  options: ["4.7", "47", "470", "0.047"],
  answer: "47",
};

export const multiplyDivideQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 6.25 × 1000?",
  options: ["625", "6250", "62500", "6.25"],
  answer: "6250",
};

export const divisionQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 890 ÷ 10?",
  options: ["89", "8.9", "8900", "0.89"],
  answer: "89",
};

export const divisionQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 5600 ÷ 100?",
  options: ["56", "560", "5.6", "0.56"],
  answer: "56",
};

export const divisionQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 7200 ÷ 1000?",
  options: ["7.2", "72", "720", "0.72"],
  answer: "7.2",
};

export const divisionQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 8.9 ÷ 10?",
  options: ["0.089", "0.89", "89", "890"],
  answer: "0.89",
};

export const divisionQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 9450 ÷ 100?",
  options: ["94.5", "945", "0.945", "9.45"],
  answer: "94.5",
};

export const multiplyByMultiplesQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 75 × 20?",
  options: ["150", "750", "1500", "7500"],
  answer: "1500",
};

export const multiplyByMultiplesQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 13 × 500?",
  options: ["650", "6500", "65000", "650000"],
  answer: "6500",
};

export const multiplyByMultiplesQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 7.5 × 200?",
  options: ["150", "1500", "15000", "75"],
  answer: "1500",
};

export const multiplyByMultiplesQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 0.25 × 4000?",
  options: ["10", "100", "1000", "10000"],
  answer: "1000",
};

export const multiplyByMultiplesQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 60 × 300?",
  options: ["1800", "18000", "180000", "1800000"],
  answer: "18000",
};

export const divisionByMultiplesQuestion1Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 180 ÷ 30?",
  options: ["6", "60", "0.6", "600"],
  answer: "6",
};

export const divisionByMultiplesQuestion2Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 5600 ÷ 200?",
  options: ["2.8", "28", "280", "2800"],
  answer: "28",
};

export const divisionByMultiplesQuestion3Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 9000 ÷ 300?",
  options: ["3", "30", "300", "3000"],
  answer: "30",
};

export const divisionByMultiplesQuestion4Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 450 ÷ 50?",
  options: ["0.9", "9", "90", "900"],
  answer: "9",
};

export const divisionByMultiplesQuestion5Data: QuestionType = {
  question: "What is 8000 ÷ 400?",
  options: ["2", "20", "200", "2000"],
  answer: "20",
};
